Viacheslav Chopyk

Front End Web Developer

Email:<u>if040489cvv@gmail.com</u>

Skype: if040489cvv

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/viacheslav-chopyk-735622170/

Personal Page: https://chopyk89.github.io/portfolio

Profile

Front End Web Developer with 2 years of commercial experience in software development mostly using Angular Framework. Familiarized with cross-browser and cross-device responsive web development. Result-orientated, responsible and attention to details. During this time I had the opportunities to work with several types of projects: Healthcare - platform healthier working environment. Internet 3D market - creating Iframe External plugin with 3D Internet of Things - platform of managing light in building E-commerce - platform of booking Creating mobile apps with Angular. Also had experience as mentor, reviewer of code or lead of front-end team on the project, creating architecture of project and project structure from scratch.

Technical Skills

Category	Skill list
Programming languages	JavaScript, TypeScript
Operating systems	Windows, Ubuntu, MacOS, Android, IOS
Libraries	Angular Material, AngularJS Material, ZingChart, Angular Bootstrap,UI-Cropper, Angular Paging, Angular Translate, RxJs, Lodash, Sweetalert, ngx-translate, Moment.JS, Moment-timezone, ng-color, ng- pick-datatime, ngx-mat-select-search, Chart.js, angular-calendar, date- fns, bootstrap 4, JQuery, Google maps, Formspree, NGRX, NGXS, Formspree, Bootstrap, WebGL, Husky, ngx-spinner, ng- image-slider, prettier, ngx-infinite-scroll, an-qrcode
Technologies	Angular 2 +, AngularJS,

Development tools	Google DevTools, Avocode, Figma, Adobe Creative Cloud, WebStorm, VS Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Android Studio, Gulp, Xcode
RDBMS	SQL, POSTGRESQL
Web	HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JADE, PUG,

SCM	Git, GitLab, Github, Bitbucket
BTS	Redmine, Trello, Jira, Gitlab board

Education

2006 - 2012

Ivano-Frankivsk National Technical University of Oil and Gas Institute of Humanities and Public Administration
Graduation degree specialist of documentation and information activities Ivano-Frankivsk, Ukraine

Languages

- English Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native

Working experience:

November 2021- May 2023 Ivano Frankivsk, Ukraine

From May 2022 - present

Develop the external site in Angular 11, with ability to configure 3D furniture in your browser, also this site (micro frontend app) used in other sites as an external feature of the primary app. (Open part of the 3D app) used in customer sites as extension.

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 8, Angular 11, AngularJS, Google DevTools, Avocode, Figma, WebStorm, WebGL

From November 2022 - present Present Role: Front-End Developer

About project: Several web sites (service), with ability to configure and buy 2D/3D models of furniture. Plugin iframe in customer site.Platform that speeds up the whole process of furniture configuration and selling. It simplifies the process of ordering and selling furniture by using interactive 3D and AR technologies. Platform allows you to change colors in real time, materials, add or remove furniture elements and get the price instantly.

Description: Change design and write or rewrite JavaScript/TypeScript, creating new projects, pages, architectures, writing custom: services, pipes, modal windows, Iframe plugins, mobile responsive, working with Unity (WebGL), bug fixing.